Hey... tell me.
Tonight,
do you want to hold me?
I want to hold you.
Okay.
Hold me.
"The Servant Prince"
(Episode 5)
I used to think that being
held by you in a place like this
made me feel like an escort.
But it's actually not so bad.
Hey.
Next time you're in the mood,
you can just call me over.
I'll come here and let you hold me.
What's wrong?
Nothing.
Honestly, just hearing you say that
is enough to get me going ten times over.
Huh?
By the way,
why would you do it alone?
Didn't I tell you
that I want you to desire me too?
What a great reaction.
That tickles.
Hey, that tickles.
Get off me. You want to go again?
Huh? Wait, Takaaki?
Hey, hey.
Where do you think you're going?
Hey, Takaaki.
Wait, what are you doing?
Come on.
Hey, that's enough. I've had enough.
Huh.
This is the first time
I've seen him sleeping.
Even though we've been
together for ten years.
During those days of painful struggle,
Naoya.
Every time I woke up,
Takaaki.
Is it time?
Takaaki was always by my side,
naturally leaning in to check on me.
Ouch...
Are you okay?
Just how tense is this
guy when he's around me?
And what kind of feelings did
he have while watching over me?
He looks a bit younger
than when he's awake.
Thank you.
Naoya?
Good morning.
Takaaki, I'm hungry.
Also, lend me a change of clothes.
I can't believe I overslept.
For a second, I didn't
even know where I was.
If I knew you were coming, I
would've bought some groceries.
There's not much to eat
in the house right now.
Anyway, I'll make you some coffee first.
Oh, sorry about that.
To think Naoya is actually here
in this dull, lifeless room.
The air here is slowly drawing
color from his presence.
Thanks.
Mhm.
It's good.
I'm glad.
Drinking coffee this elegantly
is so out of character for my daily life.
Goto Construction just announced that a
customer data breach has been confirmed.
According to the statement, the email
addresses of about 53,000 customers
and their personal
information have been leaked.
Turn off the TV.
I figured it was about time,
but this isn't exactly what you want
to hear first thing in the morning.
I remember Takaaki's company also...
[Goto Construction]
That company name...
Isn't that my dad's company?
You guys were involved in
building their security system, right?
Did you do something?
I didn't do anything.
They canceled our contract a long time ago.
Huh?
It was about half a year ago.
Goto Construction approached us, saying they
wanted to completely switch to our system.
But after looking into it, we found out
their old system was full of holes.
Even if we layered our
latest system on top of it,
there would still be a
risk of getting hacked.
So you're saying,
the security of the system my dad's
company was using was just too weak?
Exactly.
Plus, the company that built the
old system had already dissolved,
leaving almost no documentation behind.
To fix it as quickly as possible, the terms
I proposed were all within necessary costs.
I see.
From our standpoint,
we couldn't make any more concessions.
You've got quite the nerve.
I heard you're also considering
partnering with other companies.
Word travels fast.
While it's highly regrettable,
if you insist on forcing this
through with your original budget,
then we have no choice
but to terminate our partnership.
Are you sure you want to say that?
You're just a newly established startup.
The one who rejected us
and went to another company
was that man.
That guy, seriously.
He actually skimped on
investing in a management system?
It was a complete misjudgment.
So I knew this was going
to happen sooner or later.
As far as I'm concerned, he had it coming.
Let him squirm.
Fair enough.
I'm starving.
By the way,
do you not even have bread or rice here?
Sorry.
Seriously,
you don't even really live here, do you?
You're hopeless.
Let's go buy something together.
Huh?
What?
Come on, let's go.
Ah...
There are so few people
around at this hour.
There's a convenience store
just around that corner.
That's really close.
Yeah.
Man,
I kind of wanted to walk a bit longer.
This makes us look like a couple, right?
Let's go.
It's nice to do this once in a while.
Yeah.
Come to think of it,
we rarely eat breakfast together.
Whenever I woke up,
the breakfast Takaaki made for me
was always already sitting there.
Takaaki, you're still eating
salmon rice balls, huh.
And you've always stuck to tuna, Naoya.
Yeah.
Back in high school,
I used to treat you like an errand boy
and make you buy a bunch of stuff.
When they were sold out of tuna,
I'd rush all the way to a convenience store
in the next town over to get it.
Huh?
Did you really?
Naoya's orders were absolute.
I really was a jerk back then.
Takaaki.
I...
I'm actually planning
to get a full-time job.
Full-time?
Yeah.
The manager at my part-time job
asked if I wanted to go full-time.
I don't hate the work,
so I'm planning to give
her my answer today.
I see.
Is this because of that guy named Mori?
Huh?
Are you scared or something?
No, I just wanted to
know where your head's at.
Mori-san was just a catalyst.
I just want to stand
firmly on my own two feet.
If I want freedom, I need to
build a solid foundation first.
A foundation, huh.
Besides, Mori-san
is retiring this month.
Don't worry.
You're all I have.
Yeah.
Ah, we both have to get to work, right?
Let's go.
Yeah.
You're right.
You're willing to go full-time?
That's great.
Thank you.
No problem.
Now I can retire with peace of mind.
Though, with you here, Goto-kun,
I kind of want to come back to
work under the re-employment system.
Sure.
We'll be waiting for you anytime.
Mori-san was just a catalyst.
I just want to stand
firmly on my own two feet.
If I want freedom, I need to
build a solid foundation first.
Naoya is spreading his wings
and heading toward freedom.
I really should be happy for
him from the bottom of my heart.
But...
I was the one who...
That cramped little room in the past
was Naoya's everything.
I can't help but miss it terribly.
Excuse me.
President, Goto Construction is
asking about renewing the contract.
I knew they'd come.
Yes.
They said they'd like to meet
with you as soon as possible.
And they've even offered
some very generous terms.
How should we handle this?
Reject them.
Uh... but...
Just do it. Turn them down.
Yes, sir.
I understand.
I'll get back to work.
Good work.
Heading home now?
Yeah.
Want to walk together for a bit?
Sure.
I'm so glad that you're becoming a
full-time employee, Goto-san.
Not at all. I don't even know
if I can fill Mori-san's shoes.
You don't need to fill anyone's shoes.
As long as you bring your
own style to it, Goto-san,
this restaurant will definitely transform
and become even better.
What are your plans
after retiring, Mori-san?
I plan to travel the world.
It's always been a dream of mine.
After all, this is the first time
I'll have so much free time.
Free time, huh?
I was unemployed for two whole years,
and had all the free time in the world.
What was I even doing?
That just means that time
was necessary for you, too.
I...
I'll give it my all so that you won't be
disappointed when you visit again, Mori-san.
Then I'll have to buy extra souvenirs.
Huh?
I'll be looking forward to it.
At the end of the month,
Mori-san retired as planned.
Thank you for waiting.
And starting the following month, I
officially became a full-time employee.
Here is the pan-seared
sea bream with gravy.
Excuse me, where is this sea bream from?
It was caught in Hyogo Prefecture.
Goto-kun.
He's doing great.
Lately, we've even had customers coming in
specifically to see Goto-san.
Looks like he's contributing
a lot to our sales.
He really is.
It's so great that we could make
Goto-kun a full-time employee.
However, after becoming
a full-time employee,
unlike before, I'm tied up at
the restaurant for much longer.
And I've gotten much busier.
Which means my schedule
clashes with Takaaki's a lot more.
(I'm working until closing tonight,
so I'll be home late.)
(Okay.)
(I went to your place but no one was there, so
I headed back. Call me when you get off work.)
Did he really go back home
just to come over again when I got back?
Hey.
Whoa.
You were taking too long to invite me over,
so I just came by myself.
Even picked up some food on the way.
Yeah.
Hey...
You're about ready to hold me, aren't you?
Mind if I use the shower?
I haven't showered yet either.
Let's shower together then.
Shower play is an extra service, you know.
Wait, I'm gonna get dizzy.
Just get in.
(Next Episode Preview)
Maybe I should just move in here.
If it's the UNI collaboration project,
please let me handle it.
You can use this money to start a business,
or even buy a new apartment.
I want to see you more.
Because what heals me the most
is always being by Takaaki's side.